[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas：编写一个接受二进制函数的函数两次，然后
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Write a function twice that takes a binary function and
返回一个一元函数，该函数将其参数传递给二元函数两次。
returns a unary function that passes its argument to the binary function twice.
所以我说的两次是这个意思。
So by twice I mean this.
我们已经得到了Add函数，我们将把11加两次。
We've got the add function we're going to add 11 twice.
好的，那就会产生22个。
Okay, that'll produce 22.
所以我们要把它自动化。
So we're going to automate that.
我们要做两次函数。
We're gonna make a twice function.
我们可以传递Add
We can pass add to that and
它将创建一个双精度函数，它做同样的事情。
it will create a double function which does the same thing.
我们还可以将乘法函数传递给两次。
We could also pass the multiply function to twice.
它将产生一个平方函数，它将事物平方。
It will produce a square function which will square things.
现在，我故意把double这个词拼错了。
Now, I intentionally misspelled the word double.
因为在某些实现中，DOUBLE是保留字。
Because in some implementations, double is reserved word.
如果你拼写正确，你会得到一个不可原谅的语法错误。
And if you spell it correctly, you'll get a syntax error which is inexcusable.
因为Double在这种语言中甚至没有使用。
Since double isn't even used in this language.
所以，我拼错了。
But so, I misspelled it.
我建议你也因为同样的原因拼错它。
I recommend that you misspell it too for the same reason.
所以这里是两次。
So here is twice.
两次取二进制函数。
Twice takes a binary function.
返回接受参数的函数。
Returns a function that takes an argument.
返回使用该参数调用二进制函数两次的结果。
Returns result of calling the binary function with that arguments twice.
所以有两次？
So got twice?
很好，如果你没收到，就写下来。
Very good, if you didn't get it, write it down.
如果你还需要它来做另一件事的话。
If you're gonna need it for another one.
在我们继续下一个之前还有什么问题吗？
Any questions before we go on to the next one?
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：也许是一个愚蠢的问题。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Maybe a dumb question.
我试图弄清楚是否有一种方法可以使用[INAUDIBLE]来定义这一点。
I was trying to figure out if there was a way to define this using [INAUDIBLE].
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：可能有，但也许你没有这样做也是件好事。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: There probably is but it's probably just as well that you didn't.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。所以如果我们这么做了
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: All right. So if we did,
我们会想要改变到那个实现吗？
would we wanna change to that implementation?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：这取决于你。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: It's up to you.
今天最重要的是它起作用了。
The most important thing today is that it works.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：好了，准备好继续了吗？
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Okay, ready to move on?
好的，这是下一个。
Okay, here's the next one.
写反转，一个反转二进制函数参数的函数。
Write reverse, a function that reverses the arguments of a binary function.
所以我们要通过它来反转我们今天早上写的子函数。
So we're gonna to pass to reverse the sub function that we wrote this morning.
并且它返回向后减去的总线函数。
And it returns the bus function which is subtract backwards.
所以如果我们把3和2传给BUS，我们会得到-1。
So if we pass 3 and 2 to bus, we'll get -1.
好的，这里是反向的。
Okay, so here is reverse.
REVERSE接受一个二进制函数，并且
reverse takes a binary function and
返回采用第一个和第二个参数的函数，返回
returns a function that takes the first and second argument, returns
使用第二个和第一个参数调用二进制函数的结果。
result to calling the binary function with the second and first argument.
那么是谁倒转了呢？非常好。
So who got reverse? Very good.
这就是明年的写作方式。
So this is how will write it next year.
我们可以推翻任何数量的论点。
We'll be able to reverse any number of arguments.
所以我们现在正在尝试进入实用的东西。
So we're trying to get into practical stuff now.
所以你可以想象，你有两个API和
So you might imagine, you've got two APIs and
您需要让它们一起工作，但它们不是为一起工作而设计的。
you need to make them work together but they were not designed to work together.
所以他们的调用序列是不兼容的。
So they're calling sequences are incompatible.
你可以重写其中一个，使之更像另一个，但是
And you could rewrite one of them to be more like the other but
这是太多的工作，或者您可以在每个入口点周围编写一个包装函数
that's too much work or you could write a wrapper function around every entry point
但那也是太多的工作了。
of one but that's too much work too.
使用这种方法，我们可以让函数完成这项工作。
With this approach, we could let functions do that work.
所以我们可以让函数编写包装器，这将允许
So we can have functions write wrappers, which will allow
我们使用的是可操作性或互换性，好吗？
us to use the matter operability or interchangeably, okay?
准备好下一个了吗？
So ready for the next one?
编写一个函数复合，它接受两个一元函数并
Write a function composeu that takes two unary functions and
返回调用它们的一元函数。
returns a unary function that calls them both.
所以我们要在前面写的平方函数中取双精度。
So we're gonna take the double in the square function that we wrote earlier.
我们会把它们都传给Comeu
And we're gonna pass them both to composeu.
然后，我们将传递返回5的函数，它将返回100。
And then, we'll pass the function that returns 5 and it will return 100.
它会用五倍的方法来做到这一点
And it'll do that by taking the five and doubling it and
然后取下它并将其平方。
then taking that and squaring it.
所以这里是组合。
So here is composeu.
Composeu接受函数f和g。
Composeu takes functions f and g.
它返回一个函数，该函数接受参数并
It returns a function that takes an argument and
返回调用g(f(A)的结果。
returns the result of calling g(f(a)).
那么谁来给你作曲呢？
So who got compose you?
非常好。
Very good.
这个问题的棘手之处在于，嵌套函数调用是编写的
The tricky thing about this one was that nested function invocations are written
从里到外。
inside out.
从词汇上看过去
Which lexically looks backwards and
假设只需要在f之前得到g，即使稍后会调用它。
say just need to get the g before the f even though it's called later.
所以这引入了一种编程方式，有点像添加Unix管道
So this introduces a way of programming which is kind of like adding Unix pipes
除了在功能级别。
except at the function level.
我们可以利用现有的函数并将它们串在一起。
That we can take existing functions and kinda string them together.
并通过它们传递值
And pass values through them and
它将通过这个函数链，直到有东西从另一端出来。
it'll go through this chain of functions until something comes out the other end.
所以明年我们写这个函数的时候，我们会允许不是两个函数，而是
So next year when we write this function, we'll allow to take not two functions but
任何数量的函数，你可以只编程一系列的事情。
any number of functions and you can just program a whole series of things.
在此之前，您可以分别多次调用composeu
Until then, you could call composeu you several times each
向列表中添加新函数的时间。
time adding a new function to the list.
有点像加醋栗子，我想。
Sort of like currying, I guess.
好的，有什么问题吗？
Okay, any questions about that?
准备好再来一个了吗？
Ready for another one?
道格拉斯：有人吗？好的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Anybody? Yeah, all right.
好的，好的。
Good, good, all right.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：因此编写一个函数composeb，它接受两个二进制函数
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So Write a function composeb that takes two binary functions and
返回同时调用它们的函数。
returns a function that calls them both.
所以我们将通过add和
So we're going to pass add and
mul到composeb，它们将返回函数。
mul to composeb and they will return the function.
如果我们通过了，2，3，7，它就会变成35。
And if we pass it, 2, 3, and 7, it'll be turned in 35.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[咳嗽]&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：这里是composeb，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [COUGH] &gt;&gt; Douglas: So here is composeb,
composeb有两个函数f和g。
composeb takes two functions f and g.
返回接受a、b和c的函数。
Returns a function that takes a, b, and c.
并返回调用g(f(a和b)和c)的结果。
And returns result of calling g(f(a and b) and c).
那么谁得到了Composeb？
So who got composeb?
真的很好，你们做得很好。
Really good, you guys are doing great.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：感觉好吗？是吗？
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Feeling good? Yeah?
好的，想再做一次吗？
Okay, wanna do another one?
我还有一个。所以我们走吧。
I've got another one. So let's go.
编写一个限制函数，允许二进制函数
Write a limit function that allows a binary function to be
呼叫了有限的次数。
called a limited number of times.
因此，我们将把add函数传递给limit，并且
So, we're going to pass the add function to limit, and
说你可以调用它，你可以使用它一次。
say you can call it, you can use it one time.
这将产生有限的添加功能。
And that will produce a limited add function.
然后我们可以将其交给第三方，第三方可以调用它一次，并且
We could then give that to a third party, and the third party can call it once, and
它工作得恰到好处。
it works just right.
但是如果他们第二次调用，它所做的就是返回未定义的。
But if they called a second time, all it does is return undefined.
什么都不做。
Doesn't do anything else.
好的，你可以想到，你可以传递一个愿望函数来限制和
Okay, you could think of, you could pass a wish function to limit and
假设你只有三个愿望。
say you only get three wishes.
愿望函数可以实现任意数量的愿望，但
The wish function can make any number of wishes but
我们交给你的函数将会有一个限制。
the function that we hand you will have a limit on.
您传递的函数必须是二进制函数吗？
Does the function you pass have to be a binary function?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：让我们说，是的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Let's say, yes.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：将来，我们希望与任何东西合作，但不是为了
&gt;&gt; Douglas: In the future, we want to work with anything but for
今天我们只说二元函数。
today we'll just say binary function.
所以这里有限制。
So here's limit.
limit接受一个二进制函数和一个计数。
limit takes a binary function and a count.
它返回一个接受两个参数的函数。
And it returns a function that takes two arguments.
如果计数大于或等于1，则记录计数并
If the count is greater than or equal to one, it documents the count and
返回使用两个参数调用二元函数的结果。
returns the result of calling the binary function with the two arguments.
否则，将返回undefined。
Otherwise, it will return undefined.
所以从现在开始
So from this point on,
函数开始变得有点复杂了。
the functions are starting to get a little bit more complicated.
所以你不太可能和我做同样的事。
So it's unlikely that you did the same thing I did.
所以从这一点开始，我要问谁有工作的东西？
So from this point on, I'm going to ask who got something that works?
好的非常好。
Okay, very good.
有人做了什么有趣的事吗？
Anyone do something interesting?
不同的方法？
A different approach?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 3：使用一个变量而不是我有两个变量而不是只有一个变量。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Use a variable instead of I had two variables instead of just one.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：好的，你把它们放在哪里了？
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Okay, and where did you put them?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：在返回函数之前，我说了max。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Before return function, I said max.
不，麦克斯是，我说我等于零。
No, max was, I said i equal to zero.
我用的是最大数。
And the count I use max.
然后每次我运行函数，它就加1。
And then each time I run function, it just incremented i one.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：很好，非常好。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Great, very good.
还有其他人吗？
So, anybody else?
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：嗯-是的，我有点迷惑，像如何计数或。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Well- Yeah, I'm a little confused like how to count or.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：这是如何存储的，已经有多少时间了？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: How is this being stored, how the number of time has been?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：嗯，我们使用的是闭包，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Well, we're using a closure, right?
因此，另一个函数可以访问另一个函数的参数的变量
So, the other function has access to the variables of parameters of the other
功能。
function.
因此，似乎正在改变[INAUDIBLE]的计数。
So it seems the count that is changing that [INAUDIBLE].
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：您需要返回undefined吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Do you need to return undefined there?
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：是的，让我们来问一个非常好的问题。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, so let’s that a really good question.
这就是为什么在声明下划线的原因，因为我想谈谈它。
And that's why underlined the statement because I want to talk about it.
因此，关于这一说法有两种思想流派。
So, there are two schools of thought on that statement.
一个是，这是完全没有必要的。
One is, this is completely unnecessary.
因为在JavaScript中，如果函数从底部跌落，则返回undefined。
Because in JavaScript, if a function falls off the bottom it returns undefined.
所以这只是浪费空间。
So this is just a waste of space.
没有理由这样说。
There is no reason to say this.
另一种思想流派是合同的一部分
The other school of thought is that part of the contract for
这个函数是在达到限制时返回undefined。
this function is that it returns undefined when the limit is reached and so.
通过显式返回和定义，我们提供了自我文档化代码。
By explicitly returning and defined, we're providing self documenting code.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：我认为这两种观点都是正确的，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: I think both points of view are valid,
我还没能决定哪一个更好。
I've not been able to decide which one is better.
你看，你会看到我在这个问题上翻来覆去。
See, you'll see me flip flopping on this.
很明显不好的事情就是说，
The thing that is clearly bad would be saying,
只需返回分号，因为这两件事都不能完成。
just return semi colon cuz that doesn't accomplish either thing.
这是对空间的浪费，而且没有明确说明返回的内容。
It's a waste of space and it isn't explicit about what's getting returned.
怎么了？
Yes?
&GT；&GT；演讲者3：你就在这里回答了我的问题。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And you answered my question right there.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：好的，还有其他人吗？
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Okay, anybody else?
&GT；&GT；扬声器3：我有一些可能不那么聪明的东西。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I had something maybe less clever.
我有一个局部变量叫做，我把它初始化为零，
I had a local variable called, which I initialized to zero,
也就是打了多少个电话。
which was the number of calls made.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：好的，局部变量存储在-
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Okay, and the local variable was stored above-
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：是的，就像在上面，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah, it's like above the,
在回来之前。
before the return.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：太棒了，好的，非常好。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Brilliant, okay, very good.